Before today's concert, I came to see my first live performance at NHK Hall.
Two songs today.
Red, you say?
I am a little nervous.
This is our first performance at NHK Hall.
We are.
We'll do it live on stage someday.
We'll do it live on stage sometime.
We'll do it next time at NHK Hall in Osaka.
We would like to do it again in Tokyo.
Let me greet you first.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
To the hearts of the staff
Rock on!
We are the Super-Tokiimeki Advertising Department.
Please give us your best regards.
Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki Suki
I can't stop this feeling
Oh, from the day I met you
My life turned into a love song
Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki
Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki, Suki
I'm here to be with you, to be you
Suki, it's me.
I would like you to raise your own voice.
Please.
I would like to ask you to keep number 18 as it is.
I would like you to raise your voice for number 18.
It was fun.
DJ Kong during the song.
Hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo.
I really enjoyed it.
That was a lot of fun.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
Good morning.
Today, I will be performing at 2023 at LIVE IN POWER CHILD.
I'm so happy.
When I entered the room, I got honey last year, and this year too.
Jajan! Kanami.
Jan jan kanami.
Jananami, jananami.
This is acacia honey.
I have about half of it left.
I want to eat it little by little.
Valentine's Day.
Did you get this?
Oh, I see.
Oh, this is delicious.
It's Nutella.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's so cute.
I got all of them.
I got a lot of them today.
I got some yesterday, too.
What's this?
I got this.
Maybe it's Nutella.
Nutella?
Is it berry?
Thank you very much. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Now we're going to do a general earpiece monkey.
It's an earphone monkey.
I saw GUDETAMA for the first time.
It's tiny.
Cute.
It moves slowly.
It looks like it's about to collapse.
GUDETAMA is over there.
Last year, she was Cinnamon.
GUDETAMA is wearing it properly.
GUDETAMA is an adult.
It's cute.
So cute.
Risk is over.
Yay.
1?
It's 1.
Okay, I'm off to catering now.
My favorite catering.
There was Membay.
Really?
We had it last year.
Membay.
Membey.
He's really mad.
Girls' game.
Baldy.
What are you going to eat first?
I'm thinking of eating matcha.
Matcha.
There's matcha, super matte.
There's no cocoa either.
What kind of ice cream do you have?
It's ice cream without flour, eggs, milk, etc.
Oh, take that.Oh, you're going to take it.
What's that inside?
Practice matcha.
Is that so?
You should try some.
You have to eat it with your hands.
Yes, you're right.
Chocolate.
Cacao.
Matcha.
It's really close-up.
Chiria-chan.
Yay!
You've been doing this since a while ago.
It's amazing how much energy we can see on the screen.
It smells like a person's house.
Can you smell it?
Oh, it smells great.
It smells really good.
I can smell your house.
You can?
What's it smell like?
It smells good.
I've seen her and this girl have the same smell.
Isn't this the first time you've smelled it?
Is that it?
Sometimes I can tell.
What? What's that smell?
What? Is that what it smells like?
It smells like a new house.
New house smell.
Iwatoki.
Well, I wonder what it is.
I don't know.
I don't know about Riri's house either.
It smells really good.
Hiyori smells really good.
Really? Really? Yay!
It's true.
It smells really good.
It's odorless.
Hiyori's hair is always good.
Yes, it's hair.
It's beautiful.
It's more than liquid hair quality.
I'm sorry, it's not for your nose or anything.
How is it? Today's twin market.
Very nice.
Very nice?
And the bangs too, look. I had them cut.
It's so beautiful.
I had my sister cut it.
It's a little split down the middle now.
Yeah.
What do you have for catering?
There was ice cream.
Ice cream and rice crackers.
Did you eat the rice crackers?
Yes, we had ice cream.
And some ice cream that looks like a soy milk donut.
There was ice cream.
What do you think?
I want shrimp.
I'll get the UFO.
Ice cream?
I don't know.
What? What kind of onigiri is that?
But I can't eat it.
Mustard miso. What? It looks delicious.
I couldn't eat all of them because they were too spicy.
What? Let's eat takana.
Is takana spicy?
It's a little spicy, isn't it? I don't know.
Is it mustard?
Then, let's not eat it.
It would be a waste if I couldn't eat it.
This is the presentation corner.
It's a very special YouTube.
Yay!
I love it, I love it, I love it!
Perfect like!
Please give me your best wishes.
Please do.
Thank you very much.
I'll have my picture taken with you because you're extraordinarily cute.
Eeeee!
That's cheery, isn't it?
Bon appétit.
Aki-chan, you ate chocolate, didn't you?
I ate chocolate.
It's so sweet!
Soy milk is thick.
Amazake?
Ah!
What?
Oh, it's amazake!Oh, it's amazake!
It tastes like amazake mixed with green tea.
Sweet.
No color on your face.
Good work.
So cute.
So cute
You're kind of sexy, Aku.
I hate it.
Can I eat with you?
Can I? Colors.
The color looks good on you.
I like it best.
I'll eat this one until it melts.
Did you eat the regular one?
Regular.
What flavor do you want?
How do you like it?
Really?
I think it's a little fatty.
But it looks good.
Bon appétit.
Yummy.
Yum! Yum!
Isn't it important?
The position of the front hand.
Front or back?
Today it's in the back.
It's a little scary to be in the back.
But I like it.
It's so cool.
Bye-bye.
Close. Straight today.
It's so rare. My hair today.
It's my mood. Curling it makes it look mature, so I decided to straighten it.
What do you think?
durchaus
I did it!
It's a little before the show.
It's not in focus at all.
It's been a long time since we've played live.
Lots of reactions.
Thank you for watching.
Two, two, two.
I have to make a face.
Ha-ha-ha.
Huh.
I got a love shot.
Ha ha!
I always take pictures for Twitter before a show.
haha
You were doing a special digging method earlier, weren't you?
Special digging?
Bukubuku.
It's a hobby.
I learned from my teacher
I learned how to develop my voice.
Fill a plastic bottle half full with water, put a straw through it, and "buk-bugu".
Pinch your nose and blub blub blub.
I've been doing it for a long time.
My voice came out.
Yes, I did.
You'll have a low voice.
You'll have a high voice, too.
Brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Mmm.
Deden.
Pow.
Pahn.
That was a sensation.
What was that? Porch?
Yes.
Triangular pouch.
Okay.
Yellow all over.
Yellow from here, too.
Oh, it's not good at all.
Not good at all.
It's not good at all.
Look.
It's done.
What's that smell?
Yay!
Staff.
Please.
Thank you very much.
Both muscle up.
Show yourself properly.
That's right.
Just like the image.
That's not true.
So here's what we have in preparation.
Please continue watching the 2023 project on Live Embershield.
Go ahead.
Thank you for watching.
14524ading.
Now if only there was a place to go.
Loinski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski ski
Days like this.Days like this
Send us to your life
From a dream to love
From a dream to a dream
Come, together, my voice wants to emit light
Oh-kun, oh-kun, oh-kun...
Yes, that's why I was able to perform at the Live Empower Tools Live 2023 today.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
There were so many great artists at the show.
It was a lot of fun to see them.
The live performance was also very exciting.
The live show was a lot of fun, and the collaboration with DJ CO was a surprise.
I was so surprised.
Thank you very much.
He added his voice during the show.
I was able to become a star with a different kind of awareness than usual.
It was fun.
I breathed a little.
I wanted to do it.
I hope many people will smile after seeing this show.
We will try our best to perform again too.
Thank you very much.
This video introduces some of the traditional Japanese arts.
Some of the Japanese traditional arts are introduced.
Some of the traditional arts of Japan.
Yes, if you like this video, please subscribe to our channel...
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you!
We are waiting for you!
We are also waiting for your comments!
This game can also triple the attack power of the enemy, just like the American enemy.
The attack power of the enemy can be increased by 1.5 times.
The enemy's attack power can be increased by 1.5 times.
Thank you for watching.
[ED
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Hatsune Miku
Sung by Miku Hatsune